Works Progress Administration (WPA) Phonodisc Collection
Works Progress Administration (WPA) Phonodisc Collection
- 1938 season
  - Program No. 57 Works Progress Administration Presents [the] Manhattan Concert Band, 1938; wpa_phono_144; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Overture to The Magic Flute; WPA spot; Danse Macabre, Op. 40
  - Program No. 58 Works Progress Administration Presents [the] Madrigal Singers, 1938; wpa_phono_145; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    A capella singing. Hark, all ye lovely saints above; Harmonious Wedlock (Die harmonie in der ehe); Eloquent (Die beredsam keit); WPA spot; O Jesus Tender Shepherd (Ach lieber herre Jesus Christ); In Silent Night (In stille nacht); Matona, Mia Cara.
  - Program No. 59 Works Progress Administration Presents [tha] Manhattan Concert Band, 1938; wpa_phono_146; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Overture to Pique Dame; WPA spot; Malaguena, from Boabdil
  - Program No. 60 Works Progress Administration Presents Federal Symphony Orchestra, 1938; wpa_phono_147; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Symphony No. 4 in A major, Andante movement; WPA spot; Dance of the Flutes from The Nutcracker; Czar's journey from The Czar Su Han.
  - Program No. 61 Works Progress Administration Presents Manhattan Concert Band, 1938; wpa_phono_148; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Waldmere March; WPA spot; Overture to The Sicilian Vespers
  - Program No. 62 Works Progress Administration Presents Los Angeles Federal Symphony, 1938; wpa_phono_149; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Excerpts from Lenox Avenue suite, commissioned by CBS Radio: Street Scene; A Flirtation; Fight; Intervention of the Law; Dancing Boys; WPA spot; Dancing Drunkard; The Philosopher.
  - Program No. 63 Works Progress Administration Presents Los Angeles Federal Symphony and Colored Chorus, 1938; wpa_phono_150; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Excerpts from Lenox Avenue Suite, performed by men's and women's choruses: The Mission; WPA spot; The House Rent Party; The Orator; The Finale.
  - Program No. 64 Works Progress Administration Presents Los Angeles Federal Symphony and Grand Opera Chorus, 1938; wpa_phono_151; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Ave Maria from "Othello", Margaret Tietge [?] soloist with orchestra; WPA spot; Prelude to Act 3 of Lohengrin, Wedding Song, orchestra, mixed chorus, women's chorus.
  - Program No. 65 Works Progress Administration Presents Los Angeles Federal Symphony and Grand Opera Chorus, 1938; wpa_phono_152; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Prelude from Lohengrin, tenor, soprano, and basso soloists, mixed chorus, orchestra; WPA spot; King's Prayer, Finale to Act 1 from Lohengrin, Sten Englund [?] basso, orchestra.
  - Program No. 66 Works Progress Administration Presents Los Angeles Light Opera Chorus and Orchestra, 1938; wpa_phono_153; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Excerpts from the Mikado: If You Want to Know Who We Are; A wandering Minstrel, I; WPA spot; Young Man, Despair; Three little girls are we (Three maids from school); So please you sir, we much regret.
  - Program No. 67 Works Progress Administration Presents Los Angeles Light Opera Chorus and Orchestra, 1938; wpa_phono_154; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Excerpts frpm the Mikado, Act 2: Braid the Raven Hair; Madrigal: Brightly Dawns our Wedding Day; Entrance of Mikado and Katisha; A more humane Mikado; WPA spot; The Flowers that bloom in the Spring; Finale, Act 2: For he's gone and married Yum-Yum; The Threatened Cloud has Passed Away.
  - Program No. 68 Works Progress Administration Presents Los Angeles Federal Symphony, 1938; wpa_phono_155; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Largo and Minuette from Symphony no. 13 in D major; WPA spot; Traumerei
  - Program No. 69 Works Progress Administration Presents Los Angeles Colored Chorus, 1938; wpa_phono_156; folk songs and spirituals; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Joshua fit the Battle of Jericho, piano, soloists, mixed choruses; Climbin' up the Mountain Children, a capella; You may bury me in the East, female soloist with mixed chorus, a capella; WPA spot; Sinners, please, don't let this Harvest Pass, piano, men's & women's choruses; Nobody knows the Trouble I've seen, soloists, men's & women's choruses, a capella; Where shall I be when that first trumpet sounds, mixed chorus, piano.
  - Program No. 70 Works Progress Administration Presents Los Angeles Light Opera Orchestra and Colored Chorus, 1938; wpa_phono_157; selections from Fra Diavolo; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Opening Soldier's Chorus; Duet between Innkeeper's daughter Zarlina and soldier lover Lorenzo; Finale to Act 1; WPA spot; Duet between Zarlina and robber chief Fra Diavolo; Zarlina's aria; Bandits Trio; Prayer; Romanza; Finale - Victoria.
  - Program No. 71 Works Progress Administration Presents Los Angeles Federal Symphony, 1938; wpa_phono_158; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Symphonic fantasia; WPA spot; Finale from Symphony No. 13 in D major, Finale
  - Program No. 72 Works Progress Administration Presents Los Angeles Light Opera Orchestra and Chorus, 1938; wpa_phono_159; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Excerpts from H.M.S. Pinafore: Opening Chorus, orchestra; I'm Called Little Buttercup, soprano, orchestra; A Maiden Fair to See, tenor, chorus, orchestra; I am the Captain of the Pinafore, bass, chorus, orchestra; WPA spot; Refrain Audacious Tar, soprano, tenor, orchestra; Finale of Act 1, mixed chorus, orchestra.
  - Program No. 73 Works Progress Administration Presents Los Angeles Swing Orchestra, 1938; wpa_phono_160; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Basin Street Blues, Jimmy Briggs [?] vocalist, trumpet break; WPA spot; Medley composed of Confessin', The Very Thought of You, & Moonglow; Blue Skies, in the Modern Manner; instrumental with trumpet, clarinet, and sax breaks.
  - Program No. 74 Works Progress Administration Presents Los Angeles Federal Symphony and Grand Opera Chorus, 1938; wpa_phono_161; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Coronation Scene from Boris Godunov, tenor, chorus, orchestra; WPA spot; Selections from Festival Mass: Kyrie, Gloria, Sanctus, sung in Latin.
  - Program No. 75 Works Progress Administration Presents Los Angeles Light Opera Orchestra and Chorus, 1938; wpa_phono_162; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Excerpts from H.M.S. Pinafore: Bell Trio; Carefully on Tiptoe Stealing; WPA spot; Farewell, my Own, tenor, soprano, orchestra, mixed chorus; Grand Finale, entire company.
  - Program No. 76 Works Progress Administration Presents Los Angeles Federal Symphony, 1938; wpa_phono_163; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Overture to Die Meistersinger; WPA spot; Elegy
  - Program No. 77 Works Progress Administration Presents Los Angeles Colored Chorus, 1938; wpa_phono_164; folk songs and spirituals; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    I ain't gonna study war no more (a.k.a. Down by the Riverside), a capella, mixed chorus; Sooner Will Be Done, a capella, mixed chorus, tenor soloist; Daniel saw the stone, a capella, mixed chorus; WPA spot; One morning soon, a capella, male chorus; See four and twenty elders, a capella, male chorus; Some of these days; a capella, male & female choruses.
  - Program No. 78 Works Progress Administration Presents Los Angeles Federal Symphony [and Grand Opera Chorus], 1938; wpa_phono_165; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Nocturne; WPA spot; Allegro con Grazia from Symphony No. 6, 2nd movement
  - Program No. 79 Works Progress Administration Presents Los Angeles Colored Chorus, 1938; wpa_phono_166; spirituals and popular songs; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Musical setting for Shakespeare's Hamlet's Soliloquy, chorus, soloist reading; The chariot's done come and swing low, A Swing spiritual, chorus, piano accompaniment, soloists; WPA spot; Raise a ruckus tonight, chorus, soloist, a capella; Someone stole Gabriel's Horn, soloist, chorus, piano accompaniment; St. Louis Blues, soloist, chorus, piano accompaniment.
  - Program No. 80 Works Progress Administration Presents Los Angeles Federal Symphony, 1938; wpa_phono_167; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    The young prince and the young princess from Scheherazade, 3rd movement; WPA spot; St. Paul suite for strings: Ostinato
  - Program No. 81 Works Progress Administration Presents Los Angeles Swing Orchestra, 1938; wpa_phono_168; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Duke Ellington Medley: Black and Tan Fantasy, Solitude, Mood Indigo, Sophisticated Lady; Sweet is the word for you; WPA spot; My Last Affair, Chick Green [?] vocalist; All Alone.
- 1939 season
  - Program No. 1 Saxophone Sextette of Boston, 1939; wpa_phono_169; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Russian rag; Chitarra romana; Ghost dance; WPA spot; June in January, from movie "Here is my Heart"; Midnight in a madhouse
  - Program No. 2 Madrigal Singers of Boston, 1939; wpa_phono_170; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Glory to God; Woland [?]; Io mi son giovinetta; WPA spot; Echo song; Autumn Winds, Russian folk song: Autumn Winds; Now is the time of Maying
  - Program No. 3 Modern Rhythm Ensemble [and Chorus] of Boston, 1939; wpa_phono_171; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Deep Purple; Love's Old Sweet song, a.k.a. Just a Song at Twilight, chorus, orchestra, tenor soloist; WPA spot; I See Your Face Before Me, from Broadway show "Between the Devil", chorus, orchestra.
  - Program No. 4 American Folk Singers of Boston, 1939; wpa_phono_172; folk songs and spirituals; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    My Lord's Gonna move this Wicked Race, a capella, mixed chorus; I Want to Be Ready, a capella, mixed chorus, soloists; Live Humble, a capella, mixed chorus, soloists; WPA spot; Hold Out Your Light, a capella, mixed chorus; I ain't gonna study war no more, a.k.a. Down by the Riverside; a capella, mixed chorus, soloists.
  - Program No. 5 Boston State Symphony, 1939; wpa_phono_173; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Piedmontese Dance; WPA spot; Finale from Symphony No. 4
  - Program No. 6 Saxophone Sextette of Boston, 1939; wpa_phono_174; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    I'm getting sentimental over you; The dipsy doodle; WPA spot; Valse Melodic, by Harry La Forest composer; Begin the Beguine, from Jubilee
  - Program No. 7 Southland Singers, 1939; wpa_phono_175; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Hold On, soloist, mixed chorus, a capella; Bye and Bye, chorus, a capella; Heaven, chorus, a capella; WPA spot; There's Twelve Gates to the City, soloist and mixed choruses, a capella; Mary and Martha, mixed chorus, a capella; Stand the Scorn; mixed chorus, a capella.
  - Program No. 8 Manhattan Concert Band, 1939; wpa_phono_176; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Overture to Le calife de Bagdad (The Caliph of Baghdad); WPA spot; Treasure Waltz, from The Gypsy Baron
  - Program No. 9 Commonwealth Symphony and Chorus of Boston, 1939; wpa_phono_177; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Excerpts from Cavalleria Rusticana: Blossoms of oranges; Crack goes the whiplash; WPA spot; Chapel scene
  - Program No. 10 New York Civic Symphony, 1939; wpa_phono_178; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    On [in] the steppes of Central Asia; WPA spot; Dance of the Russian Sailors, from The Red Poppy
  - Program No. 11 Negro Melody Singers of New York, 1939; wpa_phono_179; folk songs and spirituals; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Sun don't set in the mornin'; Bones, come a knittin'; WPA spot; Plenty good room; No condemnation; Ride on, Jesus
  - Program No. 12 String Quartette of New York, 1939; wpa_phono_180; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Quartet in C minor, Op. 18, No. 4, 1st Movement; WPA spot; Molly on the Shore. Performers: Milton Lang [?] violin; Kalman Fleisig [?] viola; Herman Krupkoff [?] cello.
  - Program No. 13 Madrigal Singers of New York, 1939; wpa_phono_181; folk songs; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Oh, Susanna; Listen to the Mocking Bird; Poor Wayfaring Stranger, WPA spot; Brother Green, civil war mountaineers song, a capella with male & female soloists; Don't You Weep no More, Mary, Negro folk song; Old Hillbilly Roundelay: She'll be Coming Round the Mountain, a capella chorus with baritone.
  - Program No. 14 Federal Symphony of New York, 1939; wpa_phono_182; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    March from "Le coq d'or"; Dance d'esclaves from Les Troyens Ballet; WPA spot; Waltz from Swan Lake suite
  - Program No. 15 String Quartette of New York, 1939; wpa_phono_183; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Allegro non troppo from Quartet in A minor, Op. 51, No. 2; WPA spot; Romantic serenade, arranged for strings. Performers: Milton Lang [?] violin; Kalman Fleisig [?] viola; Herman Krupkoff [?] cello.
  - Program No. 16 Madrigal Singers of New York, 1939; wpa_phono_184; folk songs, including some Christmas; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Patapan, old French Christmas carol; The Dark Eyed Sailor, English folk song; Springtime of the Year, English folk song; WPA spot; Whither runneth my sweetheart, sung by duet with piano - Mable Barryman [?] soprano and James Selwood [?] tenor; The Turtle Dove, baritone, chorus, piano; Wassail or Drinking Song.
  - Program No. 17 Federal Symphony of New York, 1939; wpa_phono_185; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Prelude to La Deluge, Op. 45, Harry Nidel [?] violinist; WPA spot; Overture to Le roi l'a dit
  - Program No. 18 Negro Melody Singers of New York, 1939; wpa_phono_186; spirituals by mixed chorus and soloists; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Freedom, oh Freedom; Keep Me from sinkin' Down; Keep on a Runnin'; WPA spot; Oh Holy Land; He is King of Kings.
  - Program No. 19 New York Civic Symphony, 1939; wpa_phono_187; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Dance of the sylphs from Damnation of Faust; WPA spot; Polovtsian dances from "Prince Igor"
  - Program No. 20 Modern Rhythm Ensemble and Chorus of Boston, 1939; wpa_phono_188; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Malagueña from Andalucía; WPA spot; Western Overture: Home on the Range; Rolling Plains; Grand Canyon Suite: On The Trail; Empty Saddles from movie "Rhythm on the Range", soloist, orchestra, chorus; Pony Boy; I'm an Old Cowhand, from movie "Rhythm on the Range", chorus, orchestra; Home on the Range, reprise, soloist, chorus, orchestra.
  - Program No. 21 Commonwealth Symphony and State Chorus of Boston, 1939; wpa_phono_189; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Excerpts from I Pagliacci: Instrumental Prologue; Bell Chorus, orchestra, tenor, choruses sung in English; WPA spot; Introduction to the Act 2; Excerpts from the Act 2; Finale.
  - Program No. 22 Southland Singers of Boston, 1939; wpa_phono_190; spirituals; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    I Ain't Gonna Study War No More (Down by the Riverside), soloist, mixed chorus; Father Lazarus; I can't Sit Down; WPA spot; Oh Lord! Have Mercy on Me; Climbing Up the Mountain.
  - Program No. 23 State Symphony of Boston, 1939; wpa_phono_191; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Allegretto, 2nd movement from Symphony No. 7; WPA spot; Chinese March, from Mother Goose suite
  - Program No. 24 Manhattan Concert Band of New York, 1939; wpa_phono_192; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Prelude in G Minor; Punchinello, Op. 38; WPA spot; Overture to Martha
  - Program No. 25 Negro Melody Singers of New York, 1939; wpa_phono_193; folk songs and spirituals; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Poor Old Lazarus; I Feel Like My Time Ain't Long, soloist, chorus; Babylon's Fallen to Rise No More, soloist, mixed chorus; WPA spot; Cotton Song of the Levee, soloist, mixed chorus; Little Lize, I Love You, soloist, mixed chorus.
  - Program No. 26 State Symphony of Boston, 1939; wpa_phono_194; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Overture to The Barber of Seville; WPA spot; Waltz, from Serenade for Strings, Op. 48
  - Program No. 27 New York Civic Symphony, 1939; wpa_phono_195; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Slavonic Dance in E Minor; Deems Taylor, music composer and critic, address regarding WPA Federal Music Program; Adagio from Symphony no. 2 in C Major.
  - Program No. 28 Federal Symphony Orchestra of N.Y., 1939; wpa_phono_196; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Overture to Ruy Blas, Op. 95; Address by Dr. Thomas Parran Jr. regarding the effectiveness of the WPA program on health in general; Fandango, Op. 51, No. 2.
  - Program No. 29 Manhattan Concert Band, 1939; wpa_phono_197; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Mignonette; La danse des Demoiselles; Egyptian Dance; Charles Taussig address: A Business Man's View on the Work of the WPA; fragment of March Independentia.
  - Program No. 30 New York Civic Orchestra, 1939; wpa_phono_198; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Minuet des Follets, from the Damnation of Faust; Dorothy Canfield Fisher, author on what she thinks of the work of the WPA; Last Spring (announced as Spring).
  - Program No. 31 Federal Symphony Orchestra of N.Y., 1939; wpa_phono_199; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Nanie; Mr. Charles W. Taussig address: A Business Man's View on the Work of the WPA; Waltz in D major.
  - Program No. 32 Manhattan Concert Band, 1939; wpa_phono_200; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Overture to Il Guarany; Mr. Charles D. Maginnis, architect, address: on the Work of the WPA in the Architectural field; King Over All, Scanton [?] composer
  - Program No. 33 American Folk Singers of Boston, 1939; wpa_phono_201; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Good News, mixed chorus, soloists, a capella; Deep River, mixed chorus, a capella; Do Lord, Remember Me, mixed chorus; Hold On, mixed chorus, soloists, a capella; WPA spot; Witness for My Lord, mixed chorus, soloist, a capella.
  - Program No. 34 Federal Symphony Orchestra of N.Y., 1939; wpa_phono_202; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Overture to Egmont; WPA spot; The Dance
  - Program No. 35 Negro Melody Singers of New York, 1939; wpa_phono_203; folk songs and spirituals; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Leanin' on the Lord, men & women's choruses, soloist, arranged by Johnson Brice [?]; That Suits Me, men & women's choruses, mixed chorus, soloist; Where Shall I Go to Ease My Troubled Mind?, men & women's choruses, mixed chorus, soloist; WPA spot; E-I-O, mixed chorus, soloist, clapping, southern children's play song; Won't You Be a Witness for My Lord, mixed choruses, soloists; Good News, Chariot's Comin', mixed choruses, soloist.
  - Program No. 36 New York Civic Orchestra, 1939; wpa_phono_204; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Elegy, from the String Serenade; WPA spot; A La Balalaika, from the Opera Vengeance
  - Program No. 37 Madrigal Singers of New York, 1939; wpa_phono_205; folk songs, solo and chorus; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Burman Lover (aka The Little Canoe); Lilly Dale, sung by James Silwood [?] tenor; chorus, piano; WPA spot; The Monkey's Wedding, folk song; Lovely Fan (aka Buffalo Gals), sung by Norman Bloom, bass soloist; Frankie and Johnnie.
  - Program No. 38 Federal Symphony Orchestra of N.Y., 1939; wpa_phono_206; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Overture to Der Freischutz; WPA spot; Waltz, from Sleeping Beauty
  - Program No. 39 Federal Symphony Orchestra of Los Angeles, 1939; wpa_phono_207; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Excerpts from Bizet's Carmen: Introduction to Act II; Entr'acte music to Act IV; WPA spot; Festival music from Act IV; L'Arlesienne Suite No. 1: Aubade; Farandole.
  - Program No. 40 Grand Opera Chorus and Orchestra of Los Angeles, 1939; wpa_phono_208; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Excerpts from Bizet's Carmen: Micaela's Prayer Aria, Laura Saunders soloist; Smoking Chorus; WPA spot; Festive March of the Toreros (Entr'acte to Act IV).
  - Program No. 41 Los Angeles Dance Band, 1939; wpa_phono_209; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Goodbye, instrumental; My Reverie, instrumental; WPA spot; The Dance of the Hours, a rhythm novelty; I've Got a Pocketfull of Dreams, instrumental from movie "Sing you Sinner".
  - Program No. 42 Light Opera Company of Los Angeles, 1939; wpa_phono_210; selections from Chimes of Normandy; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    On Billow Rocking, Joseph Sullivan soloist; The Legend of the Bells, Rena Case soloist; WPA spot, With Joy in My Heart, Tom Glynn soloist; By his Side, Rena Case soloist; Quartette; Finale.
  - Program No. 43 Light Opera Company of Los Angeles, 1939; wpa_phono_211; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Excerpts from Act II of Die Fledermaus, with soloists, chorus, and orchestra: Couplets, Joseph Sullivan soloist; Czardas, sung by Rena Case soloist; WPA spot; Finale.
  - Program No. 44 Los Angeles Dance Band, 1939; wpa_phono_212; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Tio San, instrumental; Music Maestro, Please, Jack Hershong [?] soloist; WPA spot; Song of India, instrumental; Dusk in Upper Sandusky, instrumental.
  - Program No. 45 Federal Symphony Orchestra of Los Angeles, 1939; wpa_phono_213; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Maestoso-moderato, 1st movement from the Concerto Grosso in D minor; WPA spot; Idyll for Strings
  - Program No. 46 Federal Symphony of Los Angeles, 1939; wpa_phono_214; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Blue Danube waltz; WPA spot; Interlude from Gettysburg
  - Program No. 47 Federal Symphony Orchestra of Los Angeles, 1939; wpa_phono_215; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Final movement from the Concerto grosso in D minor; WPA spot; Finale to Symphony no. 4
  - Program No. 48 Federal Symphony Orchestra of Los Angeles, 1939; wpa_phono_216; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Second movement to Symphony no. 4; WPA spot; Chinese Dance from the Nutcracker Suite; Perpetuum mobile, Op. 257
  - Program No. 49 Grand Opera Chorus and Orchestra of Los Angeles, 1939; wpa_phono_217; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Excerpts from Bizet's Carmen: The Card Song; Gypsy Quintet; WPA spot; Toreador Song
  - Program No. 50 Oratorio Chorus and Federal Symphony Orchestra of Los Angeles, 1939; wpa_phono_218; selections from Les Béatitudes by César Franck; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Voice of Christ singing: Blessed he Who from Earthly Dreams Awakening, Turns his Heart from Worldly Pride, sung by Fritz Smith soloist [?]; WPA spot; Béatitudes No. 8: Stricken with Sorrow, Sad Watch I am Keeping, sung by Eunice Elder [?] soloist, and Charles De La Platte [?] soloist.
  - Program No. 51 Federal Symphony of Los Angeles, 1939; wpa_phono_219; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Second movement from the Concerto Grosso in D minor, arranged by Zilude [?]; WPA spot; Rondo Capriccioso in A minor, Op. 28, Eunice Wintermar [?] soloist.
  - Program No. 52 Federal Symphony Orchestra of Los Angeles, 1939; wpa_phono_220; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Symphony no. 2, second movement; WPA spot; Symphony no. 2, third movement, Allegretto
  - Program No. 53 Los Angeles Colored Chorus, 1939; wpa_phono_221; folk songs and spirituals; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Sooner Will be done with the Troubles of the World; Three on Record, Eddie Jones, composer [?]; No More Auction Block; WPA spot; Amen Chorus, male soloist, chorus; Tell Jesus, men & women's mixed choruses, soloist, piano accompaniment.
  - Program No. 54 Federal Symphony Orchestra, 1939; wpa_phono_222; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Prelude to La Déluge; WPA spot; Overture to Le roi l'a dit